<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="DMS_BaseTech">
    <defName>DMSE_VacuumMaterial</defName>
    <label>vacuumize process</label>
    <description>Material production in vacuum effectively avoids interference from common gases such as nitrogen and oxygen during chemical reactions. Researching materials science outside the atmosphere is especially valuable for special materials like Tantasteel, which are prone to oxidation when processed in atmospheric conditions.\n\nThis research unlocks Tantasteel production in vacuum-compatible box furnaces and sintering furnaces.</description>
    <baseCost>1000</baseCost>
    <requiredResearchBuilding Inherit="False"/>
    <teachConcept>FFF_EnvironmentalBill</teachConcept>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>DMS_Material</li>
    </prerequisites> 
    <researchViewX>2.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.50</researchViewY>
    <generalRules/>
  </ResearchProjectDef>
  
  <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="DMS_BaseTech">
    <defName>DMSE_OrbitalDynamics</defName>
    <label>orbital dynamics</label>
    <description>By studying fundamental orbital mechanics and space environmental characteristics, you can develop equipment and precision devices designed for vacuum microgravity conditions, as well as a family of specialized caseless firearms built from advanced materials.\n\nKey materials and components for this equipment rely on trade with the colonial fleet, but deeper research can eventually enable fully independent production.</description>
    <baseCost>1000</baseCost>
    <requiredResearchBuilding Inherit="False"/>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>DMS_MechBasis</li>
    </prerequisites> 
    <researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.80</researchViewY>
    <generalRules/>
  </ResearchProjectDef>
  
  <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="DMS_BaseTech">
    <defName>DMSE_Carbohydrate</defName>
    <label>Carbon synthesis</label>
    <description>Industrial-scale organic reactions can convert carbon dioxide and water into organic biomass. This "turn air into food" technology reached commercial viability before World War III, with energy conversion efficiency roughly eight to thirty times that of traditional agriculture.\n\nThis research unlocks construction of a bioreactor that consumes electricity and graphene to synthesize carbohydrates composed of starches, sugars, and other organic compounds.</description>
    <baseCost>3000</baseCost>
    <requiredResearchBuilding Inherit="False"/>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>DMS_Autofacturer</li>
      <li>DMS_Plasfiber</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>1.60</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="DMS_BaseTech">
    <defName>DMSE_Microgravity</defName>
    <label>Microgravity Manufacturing</label>
    <description>Additive manufacturing in microgravity can achieve complexity and precision far beyond what is possible under gravity. Once gravity is removed as a constant constraint, many fundamental assumptions in materials science and manufacturing are significantly altered.\n\nThis research unlocks construction of a large assembly machine for producing items in microgravity.</description>
    <baseCost>1000</baseCost>
    <requiredResearchBuilding Inherit="False"/>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>DMS_MechBasis</li>
      <li>DMSE_VacuumMaterial</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.20</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="DMS_BaseTech">
    <defName>DMSE_Aerospace</defName>
    <label>Aerospace Applications</label>
    <description>By scaling up Tantasteel and graphene production and exploring the key applications of these specialty materials in aerospace and microelectronics, this research unlocks nuclear thermal propulsion engines and orbital electronic-warfare stealth equipment for gravships and orbital starships.</description>
    <baseCost>1500</baseCost>
    <requiredResearchBuilding Inherit="False"/>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>DMSE_Microgravity</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.20</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>
</Defs>
